[
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Oosvxc BV and Fcgqkv Ltd?",
        "answer": "04-11-2006.",
        "edge": "0_1"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Fcgqkv Ltd as of 04-11-2006?",
        "answer": "Oosvxc BV.",
        "edge": "0_1"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Oosvxc BV in the contract with Fcgqkv Ltd?",
        "answer": "876 Tkpzdm Boulevard.",
        "edge": "0_1"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Oosvxc BV as of 04-11-2006?",
        "answer": "Fcgqkv Ltd.",
        "edge": "0_1"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Fcgqkv Ltd in the contract with Oosvxc BV?",
        "answer": "238 Fufjgx Circle.",
        "edge": "0_1"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Oosvxc BV and Fcgqkv Ltd?",
        "answer": "T-shirts.",
        "edge": "0_1"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Oosvxc BV and Fcgqkv Ltd?",
        "answer": "36.",
        "edge": "0_1"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Oosvxc BV and Fcgqkv Ltd?",
        "answer": "66.",
        "edge": "0_1"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Oosvxc BV and Fcgqkv Ltd?",
        "answer": "2376.",
        "edge": "0_1"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Oosvxc BV and Fcgqkv Ltd?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "0_1"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Oosvxc BV and Fcgqkv Ltd?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "0_1"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Oosvxc BV and Fcgqkv Ltd?",
        "answer": "25.",
        "edge": "0_1"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Oosvxc BV and Fcgqkv Ltd?",
        "answer": "1%.",
        "edge": "0_1"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Oosvxc BV and Fcgqkv Ltd?",
        "answer": "946 Okybcw Terrace.",
        "edge": "0_1"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Oosvxc BV and Fcgqkv Ltd?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "0_1"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Oosvxc BV and Fcgqkv Ltd?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "0_1"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Oosvxc BV and Fcgqkv Ltd?",
        "answer": "3.",
        "edge": "0_1"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Oosvxc BV and Fcgqkv Ltd?",
        "answer": "10.",
        "edge": "0_1"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Oosvxc BV and Fcgqkv Ltd?",
        "answer": "13.",
        "edge": "0_1"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Oosvxc BV and Fcgqkv Ltd?",
        "answer": "The State of North Carolina.",
        "edge": "0_1"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Kbyymf SA and Fcgqkv Ltd?",
        "answer": "26-01-2011.",
        "edge": "1_2"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Fcgqkv Ltd as of 26-01-2011?",
        "answer": "Kbyymf SA.",
        "edge": "1_2"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Kbyymf SA in the contract with Fcgqkv Ltd?",
        "answer": "132 Rlfjsb Boulevard.",
        "edge": "1_2"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Kbyymf SA as of 26-01-2011?",
        "answer": "Fcgqkv Ltd.",
        "edge": "1_2"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Fcgqkv Ltd in the contract with Kbyymf SA?",
        "answer": "238 Fufjgx Circle.",
        "edge": "1_2"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Kbyymf SA and Fcgqkv Ltd?",
        "answer": "Jeans.",
        "edge": "1_2"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Kbyymf SA and Fcgqkv Ltd?",
        "answer": "11.",
        "edge": "1_2"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Kbyymf SA and Fcgqkv Ltd?",
        "answer": "55.",
        "edge": "1_2"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Kbyymf SA and Fcgqkv Ltd?",
        "answer": "605.",
        "edge": "1_2"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Kbyymf SA and Fcgqkv Ltd?",
        "answer": "1.",
        "edge": "1_2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Kbyymf SA and Fcgqkv Ltd?",
        "answer": "10.",
        "edge": "1_2"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Kbyymf SA and Fcgqkv Ltd?",
        "answer": "25.",
        "edge": "1_2"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Kbyymf SA and Fcgqkv Ltd?",
        "answer": "1%.",
        "edge": "1_2"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Kbyymf SA and Fcgqkv Ltd?",
        "answer": "589 Iezvxq Court.",
        "edge": "1_2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Kbyymf SA and Fcgqkv Ltd?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "1_2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Kbyymf SA and Fcgqkv Ltd?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "1_2"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Kbyymf SA and Fcgqkv Ltd?",
        "answer": "3.",
        "edge": "1_2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Kbyymf SA and Fcgqkv Ltd?",
        "answer": "15.",
        "edge": "1_2"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Kbyymf SA and Fcgqkv Ltd?",
        "answer": "14.",
        "edge": "1_2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Kbyymf SA and Fcgqkv Ltd?",
        "answer": "The State of Michigan.",
        "edge": "1_2"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Kbyymf SA and Vmkocn LLC?",
        "answer": "10-06-2009.",
        "edge": "2_3"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Vmkocn LLC as of 10-06-2009?",
        "answer": "Kbyymf SA.",
        "edge": "2_3"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Kbyymf SA in the contract with Vmkocn LLC?",
        "answer": "132 Rlfjsb Boulevard.",
        "edge": "2_3"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Kbyymf SA as of 10-06-2009?",
        "answer": "Vmkocn LLC.",
        "edge": "2_3"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Vmkocn LLC in the contract with Kbyymf SA?",
        "answer": "048 Mukqth Place.",
        "edge": "2_3"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Kbyymf SA and Vmkocn LLC?",
        "answer": "Sneakers.",
        "edge": "2_3"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Kbyymf SA and Vmkocn LLC?",
        "answer": "96.",
        "edge": "2_3"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Kbyymf SA and Vmkocn LLC?",
        "answer": "54.",
        "edge": "2_3"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Kbyymf SA and Vmkocn LLC?",
        "answer": "5184.",
        "edge": "2_3"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Kbyymf SA and Vmkocn LLC?",
        "answer": "4.",
        "edge": "2_3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Kbyymf SA and Vmkocn LLC?",
        "answer": "15.",
        "edge": "2_3"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Kbyymf SA and Vmkocn LLC?",
        "answer": "25.",
        "edge": "2_3"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Kbyymf SA and Vmkocn LLC?",
        "answer": "2%.",
        "edge": "2_3"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Kbyymf SA and Vmkocn LLC?",
        "answer": "177 Znfljg Road.",
        "edge": "2_3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Kbyymf SA and Vmkocn LLC?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "2_3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Kbyymf SA and Vmkocn LLC?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "2_3"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Kbyymf SA and Vmkocn LLC?",
        "answer": "2.",
        "edge": "2_3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Kbyymf SA and Vmkocn LLC?",
        "answer": "30.",
        "edge": "2_3"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Kbyymf SA and Vmkocn LLC?",
        "answer": "9.",
        "edge": "2_3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Kbyymf SA and Vmkocn LLC?",
        "answer": "The State of California.",
        "edge": "2_3"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Vmkocn LLC and Oangph GmbH?",
        "answer": "22-10-1994.",
        "edge": "3_4"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Oangph GmbH as of 22-10-1994?",
        "answer": "Vmkocn LLC.",
        "edge": "3_4"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Vmkocn LLC in the contract with Oangph GmbH?",
        "answer": "048 Mukqth Place.",
        "edge": "3_4"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Vmkocn LLC as of 22-10-1994?",
        "answer": "Oangph GmbH.",
        "edge": "3_4"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Oangph GmbH in the contract with Vmkocn LLC?",
        "answer": "671 Nyjbfa Way.",
        "edge": "3_4"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Vmkocn LLC and Oangph GmbH?",
        "answer": "Boots.",
        "edge": "3_4"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Vmkocn LLC and Oangph GmbH?",
        "answer": "79.",
        "edge": "3_4"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Vmkocn LLC and Oangph GmbH?",
        "answer": "37.",
        "edge": "3_4"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Vmkocn LLC and Oangph GmbH?",
        "answer": "2923.",
        "edge": "3_4"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Vmkocn LLC and Oangph GmbH?",
        "answer": "4.",
        "edge": "3_4"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Vmkocn LLC and Oangph GmbH?",
        "answer": "10.",
        "edge": "3_4"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Vmkocn LLC and Oangph GmbH?",
        "answer": "20.",
        "edge": "3_4"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Vmkocn LLC and Oangph GmbH?",
        "answer": "5%.",
        "edge": "3_4"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Vmkocn LLC and Oangph GmbH?",
        "answer": "525 Noruik Way.",
        "edge": "3_4"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Vmkocn LLC and Oangph GmbH?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "3_4"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Vmkocn LLC and Oangph GmbH?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "3_4"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Vmkocn LLC and Oangph GmbH?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "3_4"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Vmkocn LLC and Oangph GmbH?",
        "answer": "25.",
        "edge": "3_4"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Vmkocn LLC and Oangph GmbH?",
        "answer": "6.",
        "edge": "3_4"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Vmkocn LLC and Oangph GmbH?",
        "answer": "The State of Pennsylvania.",
        "edge": "3_4"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Iqfajp AG and Oangph GmbH?",
        "answer": "18-02-1982.",
        "edge": "4_5"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Oangph GmbH as of 18-02-1982?",
        "answer": "Iqfajp AG.",
        "edge": "4_5"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Iqfajp AG in the contract with Oangph GmbH?",
        "answer": "508 Xskmjt Lane.",
        "edge": "4_5"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Iqfajp AG as of 18-02-1982?",
        "answer": "Oangph GmbH.",
        "edge": "4_5"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Oangph GmbH in the contract with Iqfajp AG?",
        "answer": "671 Nyjbfa Way.",
        "edge": "4_5"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Iqfajp AG and Oangph GmbH?",
        "answer": "Scarves.",
        "edge": "4_5"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Iqfajp AG and Oangph GmbH?",
        "answer": "24.",
        "edge": "4_5"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Iqfajp AG and Oangph GmbH?",
        "answer": "56.",
        "edge": "4_5"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Iqfajp AG and Oangph GmbH?",
        "answer": "1344.",
        "edge": "4_5"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Iqfajp AG and Oangph GmbH?",
        "answer": "2.",
        "edge": "4_5"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Iqfajp AG and Oangph GmbH?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "4_5"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Iqfajp AG and Oangph GmbH?",
        "answer": "30.",
        "edge": "4_5"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Iqfajp AG and Oangph GmbH?",
        "answer": "1%.",
        "edge": "4_5"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Iqfajp AG and Oangph GmbH?",
        "answer": "462 Iovfgu Circle.",
        "edge": "4_5"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Iqfajp AG and Oangph GmbH?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "4_5"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Iqfajp AG and Oangph GmbH?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "4_5"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Iqfajp AG and Oangph GmbH?",
        "answer": "4.",
        "edge": "4_5"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Iqfajp AG and Oangph GmbH?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "4_5"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Iqfajp AG and Oangph GmbH?",
        "answer": "6.",
        "edge": "4_5"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Iqfajp AG and Oangph GmbH?",
        "answer": "The State of Florida.",
        "edge": "4_5"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Iqfajp AG and Idtbha SAS?",
        "answer": "02-04-2017.",
        "edge": "5_6"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Idtbha SAS as of 02-04-2017?",
        "answer": "Iqfajp AG.",
        "edge": "5_6"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Iqfajp AG in the contract with Idtbha SAS?",
        "answer": "508 Xskmjt Lane.",
        "edge": "5_6"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Iqfajp AG as of 02-04-2017?",
        "answer": "Idtbha SAS.",
        "edge": "5_6"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Idtbha SAS in the contract with Iqfajp AG?",
        "answer": "924 Bggrxi Drive.",
        "edge": "5_6"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Iqfajp AG and Idtbha SAS?",
        "answer": "Rings.",
        "edge": "5_6"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Iqfajp AG and Idtbha SAS?",
        "answer": "44.",
        "edge": "5_6"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Iqfajp AG and Idtbha SAS?",
        "answer": "83.",
        "edge": "5_6"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Iqfajp AG and Idtbha SAS?",
        "answer": "3652.",
        "edge": "5_6"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Iqfajp AG and Idtbha SAS?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "5_6"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Iqfajp AG and Idtbha SAS?",
        "answer": "10.",
        "edge": "5_6"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Iqfajp AG and Idtbha SAS?",
        "answer": "15.",
        "edge": "5_6"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Iqfajp AG and Idtbha SAS?",
        "answer": "3%.",
        "edge": "5_6"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Iqfajp AG and Idtbha SAS?",
        "answer": "256 Jnmvwj Alley.",
        "edge": "5_6"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Iqfajp AG and Idtbha SAS?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "5_6"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Iqfajp AG and Idtbha SAS?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "5_6"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Iqfajp AG and Idtbha SAS?",
        "answer": "1.",
        "edge": "5_6"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Iqfajp AG and Idtbha SAS?",
        "answer": "10.",
        "edge": "5_6"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Iqfajp AG and Idtbha SAS?",
        "answer": "8.",
        "edge": "5_6"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Iqfajp AG and Idtbha SAS?",
        "answer": "The State of North Carolina.",
        "edge": "5_6"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Idtbha SAS and Zxgckl Ltd?",
        "answer": "03-05-2010.",
        "edge": "6_7"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Zxgckl Ltd as of 03-05-2010?",
        "answer": "Idtbha SAS.",
        "edge": "6_7"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Idtbha SAS in the contract with Zxgckl Ltd?",
        "answer": "924 Bggrxi Drive.",
        "edge": "6_7"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Idtbha SAS as of 03-05-2010?",
        "answer": "Zxgckl Ltd.",
        "edge": "6_7"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Zxgckl Ltd in the contract with Idtbha SAS?",
        "answer": "136 Pvufat Terrace.",
        "edge": "6_7"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Idtbha SAS and Zxgckl Ltd?",
        "answer": "Necklaces.",
        "edge": "6_7"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Idtbha SAS and Zxgckl Ltd?",
        "answer": "85.",
        "edge": "6_7"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Idtbha SAS and Zxgckl Ltd?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "6_7"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Idtbha SAS and Zxgckl Ltd?",
        "answer": "425.",
        "edge": "6_7"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Idtbha SAS and Zxgckl Ltd?",
        "answer": "1.",
        "edge": "6_7"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Idtbha SAS and Zxgckl Ltd?",
        "answer": "25.",
        "edge": "6_7"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Idtbha SAS and Zxgckl Ltd?",
        "answer": "10.",
        "edge": "6_7"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Idtbha SAS and Zxgckl Ltd?",
        "answer": "3%.",
        "edge": "6_7"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Idtbha SAS and Zxgckl Ltd?",
        "answer": "390 Fpyweb Avenue.",
        "edge": "6_7"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Idtbha SAS and Zxgckl Ltd?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "6_7"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Idtbha SAS and Zxgckl Ltd?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "6_7"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Idtbha SAS and Zxgckl Ltd?",
        "answer": "4.",
        "edge": "6_7"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Idtbha SAS and Zxgckl Ltd?",
        "answer": "15.",
        "edge": "6_7"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Idtbha SAS and Zxgckl Ltd?",
        "answer": "14.",
        "edge": "6_7"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Idtbha SAS and Zxgckl Ltd?",
        "answer": "The State of New York.",
        "edge": "6_7"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Ixpayl SARL and Zxgckl Ltd?",
        "answer": "06-05-2005.",
        "edge": "7_8"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Zxgckl Ltd as of 06-05-2005?",
        "answer": "Ixpayl SARL.",
        "edge": "7_8"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Ixpayl SARL in the contract with Zxgckl Ltd?",
        "answer": "695 Quglfi Place.",
        "edge": "7_8"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Ixpayl SARL as of 06-05-2005?",
        "answer": "Zxgckl Ltd.",
        "edge": "7_8"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Zxgckl Ltd in the contract with Ixpayl SARL?",
        "answer": "136 Pvufat Terrace.",
        "edge": "7_8"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Ixpayl SARL and Zxgckl Ltd?",
        "answer": "Watches.",
        "edge": "7_8"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Ixpayl SARL and Zxgckl Ltd?",
        "answer": "95.",
        "edge": "7_8"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Ixpayl SARL and Zxgckl Ltd?",
        "answer": "63.",
        "edge": "7_8"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Ixpayl SARL and Zxgckl Ltd?",
        "answer": "5985.",
        "edge": "7_8"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Ixpayl SARL and Zxgckl Ltd?",
        "answer": "1.",
        "edge": "7_8"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Ixpayl SARL and Zxgckl Ltd?",
        "answer": "10.",
        "edge": "7_8"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Ixpayl SARL and Zxgckl Ltd?",
        "answer": "25.",
        "edge": "7_8"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Ixpayl SARL and Zxgckl Ltd?",
        "answer": "3%.",
        "edge": "7_8"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Ixpayl SARL and Zxgckl Ltd?",
        "answer": "290 Gsggrd Street.",
        "edge": "7_8"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Ixpayl SARL and Zxgckl Ltd?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "7_8"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Ixpayl SARL and Zxgckl Ltd?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "7_8"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Ixpayl SARL and Zxgckl Ltd?",
        "answer": "2.",
        "edge": "7_8"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Ixpayl SARL and Zxgckl Ltd?",
        "answer": "15.",
        "edge": "7_8"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Ixpayl SARL and Zxgckl Ltd?",
        "answer": "14.",
        "edge": "7_8"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Ixpayl SARL and Zxgckl Ltd?",
        "answer": "The State of Texas.",
        "edge": "7_8"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Dqchpy Inc and Ixpayl SARL?",
        "answer": "27-07-2019.",
        "edge": "8_9"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Ixpayl SARL as of 27-07-2019?",
        "answer": "Dqchpy Inc.",
        "edge": "8_9"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Dqchpy Inc in the contract with Ixpayl SARL?",
        "answer": "679 Zfycek Highway.",
        "edge": "8_9"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Dqchpy Inc as of 27-07-2019?",
        "answer": "Ixpayl SARL.",
        "edge": "8_9"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Ixpayl SARL in the contract with Dqchpy Inc?",
        "answer": "695 Quglfi Place.",
        "edge": "8_9"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Dqchpy Inc and Ixpayl SARL?",
        "answer": "Handbags.",
        "edge": "8_9"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Dqchpy Inc and Ixpayl SARL?",
        "answer": "98.",
        "edge": "8_9"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Dqchpy Inc and Ixpayl SARL?",
        "answer": "75.",
        "edge": "8_9"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Dqchpy Inc and Ixpayl SARL?",
        "answer": "7350.",
        "edge": "8_9"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Dqchpy Inc and Ixpayl SARL?",
        "answer": "2.",
        "edge": "8_9"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Dqchpy Inc and Ixpayl SARL?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "8_9"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Dqchpy Inc and Ixpayl SARL?",
        "answer": "30.",
        "edge": "8_9"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Dqchpy Inc and Ixpayl SARL?",
        "answer": "3%.",
        "edge": "8_9"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Dqchpy Inc and Ixpayl SARL?",
        "answer": "407 Efogwy Highway.",
        "edge": "8_9"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Dqchpy Inc and Ixpayl SARL?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "8_9"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Dqchpy Inc and Ixpayl SARL?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "8_9"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Dqchpy Inc and Ixpayl SARL?",
        "answer": "1.",
        "edge": "8_9"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Dqchpy Inc and Ixpayl SARL?",
        "answer": "25.",
        "edge": "8_9"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Dqchpy Inc and Ixpayl SARL?",
        "answer": "4.",
        "edge": "8_9"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Dqchpy Inc and Ixpayl SARL?",
        "answer": "The State of Florida.",
        "edge": "8_9"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "06-12-2011.",
        "edge": "10_11"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Ogcgwj LLC as of 06-12-2011?",
        "answer": "Mlyqwh SRL.",
        "edge": "10_11"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Mlyqwh SRL in the contract with Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "240 Pqpjop Drive.",
        "edge": "10_11"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Mlyqwh SRL as of 06-12-2011?",
        "answer": "Ogcgwj LLC.",
        "edge": "10_11"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Ogcgwj LLC in the contract with Mlyqwh SRL?",
        "answer": "850 Uqyxwh Square.",
        "edge": "10_11"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "Sunglasses.",
        "edge": "10_11"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "17.",
        "edge": "10_11"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "38.",
        "edge": "10_11"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "646.",
        "edge": "10_11"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "4.",
        "edge": "10_11"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "25.",
        "edge": "10_11"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "30.",
        "edge": "10_11"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "2%.",
        "edge": "10_11"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "481 Povcna Lane.",
        "edge": "10_11"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "10_11"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "10_11"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "1.",
        "edge": "10_11"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "20.",
        "edge": "10_11"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "14.",
        "edge": "10_11"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "The State of New York.",
        "edge": "10_11"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Mlyqwh SRL?",
        "answer": "10-04-2012.",
        "edge": "11_12"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Mlyqwh SRL as of 10-04-2012?",
        "answer": "Gjrtoz AG.",
        "edge": "11_12"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Gjrtoz AG in the contract with Mlyqwh SRL?",
        "answer": "796 Vtrlha Place.",
        "edge": "11_12"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Gjrtoz AG as of 10-04-2012?",
        "answer": "Mlyqwh SRL.",
        "edge": "11_12"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Mlyqwh SRL in the contract with Gjrtoz AG?",
        "answer": "240 Pqpjop Drive.",
        "edge": "11_12"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Mlyqwh SRL?",
        "answer": "Smartphones.",
        "edge": "11_12"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Mlyqwh SRL?",
        "answer": "50.",
        "edge": "11_12"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Mlyqwh SRL?",
        "answer": "22.",
        "edge": "11_12"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Mlyqwh SRL?",
        "answer": "1100.",
        "edge": "11_12"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Mlyqwh SRL?",
        "answer": "4.",
        "edge": "11_12"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Mlyqwh SRL?",
        "answer": "10.",
        "edge": "11_12"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Mlyqwh SRL?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "11_12"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Mlyqwh SRL?",
        "answer": "1%.",
        "edge": "11_12"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Mlyqwh SRL?",
        "answer": "721 Qcmowk Court.",
        "edge": "11_12"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Mlyqwh SRL?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "11_12"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Mlyqwh SRL?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "11_12"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Mlyqwh SRL?",
        "answer": "2.",
        "edge": "11_12"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Mlyqwh SRL?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "11_12"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Mlyqwh SRL?",
        "answer": "10.",
        "edge": "11_12"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Mlyqwh SRL?",
        "answer": "The State of Michigan.",
        "edge": "11_12"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "17-12-1982.",
        "edge": "12_13"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Rlnhbo GmbH as of 17-12-1982?",
        "answer": "Gjrtoz AG.",
        "edge": "12_13"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Gjrtoz AG in the contract with Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "796 Vtrlha Place.",
        "edge": "12_13"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Gjrtoz AG as of 17-12-1982?",
        "answer": "Rlnhbo GmbH.",
        "edge": "12_13"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Rlnhbo GmbH in the contract with Gjrtoz AG?",
        "answer": "903 Dvklfj Boulevard.",
        "edge": "12_13"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "Laptop computers.",
        "edge": "12_13"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "34.",
        "edge": "12_13"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "89.",
        "edge": "12_13"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "3026.",
        "edge": "12_13"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "12_13"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "20.",
        "edge": "12_13"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "10.",
        "edge": "12_13"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "1%.",
        "edge": "12_13"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "665 Wrjtnh Alley.",
        "edge": "12_13"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "12_13"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "12_13"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "12_13"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "20.",
        "edge": "12_13"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "9.",
        "edge": "12_13"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "The State of New York.",
        "edge": "12_13"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Ntquss BV and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "05-02-1994.",
        "edge": "13_14"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Rlnhbo GmbH as of 05-02-1994?",
        "answer": "Ntquss BV.",
        "edge": "13_14"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Ntquss BV in the contract with Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "294 Wrhxts Court.",
        "edge": "13_14"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Ntquss BV as of 05-02-1994?",
        "answer": "Rlnhbo GmbH.",
        "edge": "13_14"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Rlnhbo GmbH in the contract with Ntquss BV?",
        "answer": "903 Dvklfj Boulevard.",
        "edge": "13_14"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Ntquss BV and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "Video recorder.",
        "edge": "13_14"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Ntquss BV and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "25.",
        "edge": "13_14"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Ntquss BV and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "27.",
        "edge": "13_14"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Ntquss BV and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "675.",
        "edge": "13_14"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Ntquss BV and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "2.",
        "edge": "13_14"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Ntquss BV and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "15.",
        "edge": "13_14"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Ntquss BV and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "25.",
        "edge": "13_14"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Ntquss BV and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "3%.",
        "edge": "13_14"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Ntquss BV and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "347 Wxvvkd Square.",
        "edge": "13_14"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Ntquss BV and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "13_14"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Ntquss BV and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "13_14"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Ntquss BV and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "3.",
        "edge": "13_14"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Ntquss BV and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "13_14"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Ntquss BV and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "8.",
        "edge": "13_14"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Ntquss BV and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "The State of Michigan.",
        "edge": "13_14"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Ntquss BV and Hioruo LLC?",
        "answer": "04-05-1994.",
        "edge": "14_15"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Hioruo LLC as of 04-05-1994?",
        "answer": "Ntquss BV.",
        "edge": "14_15"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Ntquss BV in the contract with Hioruo LLC?",
        "answer": "294 Wrhxts Court.",
        "edge": "14_15"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Ntquss BV as of 04-05-1994?",
        "answer": "Hioruo LLC.",
        "edge": "14_15"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Hioruo LLC in the contract with Ntquss BV?",
        "answer": "632 Gwjmfp Street.",
        "edge": "14_15"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Ntquss BV and Hioruo LLC?",
        "answer": "iPads.",
        "edge": "14_15"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Ntquss BV and Hioruo LLC?",
        "answer": "44.",
        "edge": "14_15"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Ntquss BV and Hioruo LLC?",
        "answer": "15.",
        "edge": "14_15"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Ntquss BV and Hioruo LLC?",
        "answer": "660.",
        "edge": "14_15"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Ntquss BV and Hioruo LLC?",
        "answer": "4.",
        "edge": "14_15"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Ntquss BV and Hioruo LLC?",
        "answer": "10.",
        "edge": "14_15"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Ntquss BV and Hioruo LLC?",
        "answer": "30.",
        "edge": "14_15"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Ntquss BV and Hioruo LLC?",
        "answer": "5%.",
        "edge": "14_15"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Ntquss BV and Hioruo LLC?",
        "answer": "492 Njrbyk Highway.",
        "edge": "14_15"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Ntquss BV and Hioruo LLC?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "14_15"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Ntquss BV and Hioruo LLC?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "14_15"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Ntquss BV and Hioruo LLC?",
        "answer": "4.",
        "edge": "14_15"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Ntquss BV and Hioruo LLC?",
        "answer": "15.",
        "edge": "14_15"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Ntquss BV and Hioruo LLC?",
        "answer": "11.",
        "edge": "14_15"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Ntquss BV and Hioruo LLC?",
        "answer": "The State of Pennsylvania.",
        "edge": "14_15"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Hioruo LLC and Gytgwd LLC?",
        "answer": "09-01-2011.",
        "edge": "15_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Gytgwd LLC as of 09-01-2011?",
        "answer": "Hioruo LLC.",
        "edge": "15_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Hioruo LLC in the contract with Gytgwd LLC?",
        "answer": "632 Gwjmfp Street.",
        "edge": "15_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Hioruo LLC as of 09-01-2011?",
        "answer": "Gytgwd LLC.",
        "edge": "15_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Gytgwd LLC in the contract with Hioruo LLC?",
        "answer": "966 Wvdpav Alley.",
        "edge": "15_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Hioruo LLC and Gytgwd LLC?",
        "answer": "Headphones.",
        "edge": "15_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Hioruo LLC and Gytgwd LLC?",
        "answer": "45.",
        "edge": "15_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Hioruo LLC and Gytgwd LLC?",
        "answer": "41.",
        "edge": "15_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Hioruo LLC and Gytgwd LLC?",
        "answer": "1845.",
        "edge": "15_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Hioruo LLC and Gytgwd LLC?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "15_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Hioruo LLC and Gytgwd LLC?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "15_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Hioruo LLC and Gytgwd LLC?",
        "answer": "20.",
        "edge": "15_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Hioruo LLC and Gytgwd LLC?",
        "answer": "5%.",
        "edge": "15_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Hioruo LLC and Gytgwd LLC?",
        "answer": "658 Sahodw Crescent.",
        "edge": "15_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Hioruo LLC and Gytgwd LLC?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "15_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Hioruo LLC and Gytgwd LLC?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "15_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Hioruo LLC and Gytgwd LLC?",
        "answer": "4.",
        "edge": "15_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Hioruo LLC and Gytgwd LLC?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "15_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Hioruo LLC and Gytgwd LLC?",
        "answer": "13.",
        "edge": "15_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Hioruo LLC and Gytgwd LLC?",
        "answer": "The State of Georgia.",
        "edge": "15_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Hqopns SRL?",
        "answer": "29-09-2019.",
        "edge": "16_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Hqopns SRL as of 29-09-2019?",
        "answer": "Gytgwd LLC.",
        "edge": "16_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Gytgwd LLC in the contract with Hqopns SRL?",
        "answer": "966 Wvdpav Alley.",
        "edge": "16_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Gytgwd LLC as of 29-09-2019?",
        "answer": "Hqopns SRL.",
        "edge": "16_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Hqopns SRL in the contract with Gytgwd LLC?",
        "answer": "813 Gilzsr Place.",
        "edge": "16_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Hqopns SRL?",
        "answer": "Sofas.",
        "edge": "16_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Hqopns SRL?",
        "answer": "81.",
        "edge": "16_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Hqopns SRL?",
        "answer": "59.",
        "edge": "16_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Hqopns SRL?",
        "answer": "4779.",
        "edge": "16_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Hqopns SRL?",
        "answer": "2.",
        "edge": "16_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Hqopns SRL?",
        "answer": "30.",
        "edge": "16_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Hqopns SRL?",
        "answer": "30.",
        "edge": "16_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Hqopns SRL?",
        "answer": "3%.",
        "edge": "16_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Hqopns SRL?",
        "answer": "818 Glrkip Street.",
        "edge": "16_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Hqopns SRL?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "16_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Hqopns SRL?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "16_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Hqopns SRL?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "16_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Hqopns SRL?",
        "answer": "20.",
        "edge": "16_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Hqopns SRL?",
        "answer": "7.",
        "edge": "16_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Hqopns SRL?",
        "answer": "The State of Pennsylvania.",
        "edge": "16_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Hqopns SRL and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "02-06-1990.",
        "edge": "17_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Stxiik BVBA as of 02-06-1990?",
        "answer": "Hqopns SRL.",
        "edge": "17_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Hqopns SRL in the contract with Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "813 Gilzsr Place.",
        "edge": "17_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Hqopns SRL as of 02-06-1990?",
        "answer": "Stxiik BVBA.",
        "edge": "17_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Stxiik BVBA in the contract with Hqopns SRL?",
        "answer": "818 Xbwjoi Street.",
        "edge": "17_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Hqopns SRL and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "Dining tables.",
        "edge": "17_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Hqopns SRL and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "21.",
        "edge": "17_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Hqopns SRL and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "58.",
        "edge": "17_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Hqopns SRL and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "1218.",
        "edge": "17_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Hqopns SRL and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "1.",
        "edge": "17_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Hqopns SRL and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "30.",
        "edge": "17_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Hqopns SRL and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "25.",
        "edge": "17_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Hqopns SRL and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "3%.",
        "edge": "17_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Hqopns SRL and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "933 Ymlqda Way.",
        "edge": "17_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Hqopns SRL and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "17_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Hqopns SRL and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "17_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Hqopns SRL and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "17_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Hqopns SRL and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "25.",
        "edge": "17_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Hqopns SRL and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "4.",
        "edge": "17_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Hqopns SRL and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "The State of North Carolina.",
        "edge": "17_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Stxiik BVBA and Gadwnx SA?",
        "answer": "22-03-1989.",
        "edge": "18_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Gadwnx SA as of 22-03-1989?",
        "answer": "Stxiik BVBA.",
        "edge": "18_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Stxiik BVBA in the contract with Gadwnx SA?",
        "answer": "818 Xbwjoi Street.",
        "edge": "18_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Stxiik BVBA as of 22-03-1989?",
        "answer": "Gadwnx SA.",
        "edge": "18_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Gadwnx SA in the contract with Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "290 Gxgyre Alley.",
        "edge": "18_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Stxiik BVBA and Gadwnx SA?",
        "answer": "Shoe storages.",
        "edge": "18_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Stxiik BVBA and Gadwnx SA?",
        "answer": "20.",
        "edge": "18_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Stxiik BVBA and Gadwnx SA?",
        "answer": "20.",
        "edge": "18_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Stxiik BVBA and Gadwnx SA?",
        "answer": "400.",
        "edge": "18_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Stxiik BVBA and Gadwnx SA?",
        "answer": "4.",
        "edge": "18_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Stxiik BVBA and Gadwnx SA?",
        "answer": "20.",
        "edge": "18_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Stxiik BVBA and Gadwnx SA?",
        "answer": "30.",
        "edge": "18_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Stxiik BVBA and Gadwnx SA?",
        "answer": "3%.",
        "edge": "18_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Stxiik BVBA and Gadwnx SA?",
        "answer": "618 Ouhnzd Court.",
        "edge": "18_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Stxiik BVBA and Gadwnx SA?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "18_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Stxiik BVBA and Gadwnx SA?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "18_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Stxiik BVBA and Gadwnx SA?",
        "answer": "2.",
        "edge": "18_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Stxiik BVBA and Gadwnx SA?",
        "answer": "25.",
        "edge": "18_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Stxiik BVBA and Gadwnx SA?",
        "answer": "3.",
        "edge": "18_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Stxiik BVBA and Gadwnx SA?",
        "answer": "The State of Illinois.",
        "edge": "18_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Gadwnx SA and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "24-03-2010.",
        "edge": "10_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Ogcgwj LLC as of 24-03-2010?",
        "answer": "Gadwnx SA.",
        "edge": "10_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Gadwnx SA in the contract with Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "290 Gxgyre Alley.",
        "edge": "10_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Gadwnx SA as of 24-03-2010?",
        "answer": "Ogcgwj LLC.",
        "edge": "10_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Ogcgwj LLC in the contract with Gadwnx SA?",
        "answer": "850 Uqyxwh Square.",
        "edge": "10_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Gadwnx SA and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "TV stands.",
        "edge": "10_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Gadwnx SA and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "81.",
        "edge": "10_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Gadwnx SA and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "64.",
        "edge": "10_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Gadwnx SA and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "5184.",
        "edge": "10_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Gadwnx SA and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "3.",
        "edge": "10_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Gadwnx SA and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "10_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Gadwnx SA and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "30.",
        "edge": "10_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Gadwnx SA and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "5%.",
        "edge": "10_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Gadwnx SA and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "262 Zsbggy Drive.",
        "edge": "10_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Gadwnx SA and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "10_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Gadwnx SA and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "10_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Gadwnx SA and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "2.",
        "edge": "10_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Gadwnx SA and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "10_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Gadwnx SA and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "13.",
        "edge": "10_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Gadwnx SA and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "The State of Michigan.",
        "edge": "10_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "23-10-2010.",
        "edge": "11_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Stxiik BVBA as of 23-10-2010?",
        "answer": "Mlyqwh SRL.",
        "edge": "11_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Mlyqwh SRL in the contract with Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "240 Pqpjop Drive.",
        "edge": "11_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Mlyqwh SRL as of 23-10-2010?",
        "answer": "Stxiik BVBA.",
        "edge": "11_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Stxiik BVBA in the contract with Mlyqwh SRL?",
        "answer": "818 Xbwjoi Street.",
        "edge": "11_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "Armchairs.",
        "edge": "11_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "87.",
        "edge": "11_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "12.",
        "edge": "11_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "1044.",
        "edge": "11_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "11_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "10.",
        "edge": "11_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "20.",
        "edge": "11_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "1%.",
        "edge": "11_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "830 Maymbk Square.",
        "edge": "11_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "11_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "11_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "11_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "15.",
        "edge": "11_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "7.",
        "edge": "11_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "The State of Ohio.",
        "edge": "11_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Hqopns SRL and Gjrtoz AG?",
        "answer": "28-09-2001.",
        "edge": "12_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Gjrtoz AG as of 28-09-2001?",
        "answer": "Hqopns SRL.",
        "edge": "12_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Hqopns SRL in the contract with Gjrtoz AG?",
        "answer": "813 Gilzsr Place.",
        "edge": "12_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Hqopns SRL as of 28-09-2001?",
        "answer": "Gjrtoz AG.",
        "edge": "12_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Gjrtoz AG in the contract with Hqopns SRL?",
        "answer": "796 Vtrlha Place.",
        "edge": "12_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Hqopns SRL and Gjrtoz AG?",
        "answer": "Pillows.",
        "edge": "12_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Hqopns SRL and Gjrtoz AG?",
        "answer": "56.",
        "edge": "12_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Hqopns SRL and Gjrtoz AG?",
        "answer": "4.",
        "edge": "12_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Hqopns SRL and Gjrtoz AG?",
        "answer": "224.",
        "edge": "12_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Hqopns SRL and Gjrtoz AG?",
        "answer": "4.",
        "edge": "12_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Hqopns SRL and Gjrtoz AG?",
        "answer": "25.",
        "edge": "12_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Hqopns SRL and Gjrtoz AG?",
        "answer": "10.",
        "edge": "12_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Hqopns SRL and Gjrtoz AG?",
        "answer": "4%.",
        "edge": "12_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Hqopns SRL and Gjrtoz AG?",
        "answer": "051 Yriqrs Boulevard.",
        "edge": "12_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Hqopns SRL and Gjrtoz AG?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "12_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Hqopns SRL and Gjrtoz AG?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "12_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Hqopns SRL and Gjrtoz AG?",
        "answer": "2.",
        "edge": "12_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Hqopns SRL and Gjrtoz AG?",
        "answer": "30.",
        "edge": "12_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Hqopns SRL and Gjrtoz AG?",
        "answer": "10.",
        "edge": "12_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Hqopns SRL and Gjrtoz AG?",
        "answer": "The State of New York.",
        "edge": "12_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "11-01-1992.",
        "edge": "13_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Rlnhbo GmbH as of 11-01-1992?",
        "answer": "Gytgwd LLC.",
        "edge": "13_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Gytgwd LLC in the contract with Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "966 Wvdpav Alley.",
        "edge": "13_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Gytgwd LLC as of 11-01-1992?",
        "answer": "Rlnhbo GmbH.",
        "edge": "13_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Rlnhbo GmbH in the contract with Gytgwd LLC?",
        "answer": "903 Dvklfj Boulevard.",
        "edge": "13_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "Blankets.",
        "edge": "13_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "66.",
        "edge": "13_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "57.",
        "edge": "13_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "3762.",
        "edge": "13_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "2.",
        "edge": "13_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "20.",
        "edge": "13_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "25.",
        "edge": "13_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "2%.",
        "edge": "13_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "925 Snoymg Crescent.",
        "edge": "13_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "13_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "13_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "1.",
        "edge": "13_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "13_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "4.",
        "edge": "13_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "The State of Illinois.",
        "edge": "13_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Stxiik BVBA and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "18-09-2007.",
        "edge": "10_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Ogcgwj LLC as of 18-09-2007?",
        "answer": "Stxiik BVBA.",
        "edge": "10_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Stxiik BVBA in the contract with Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "818 Xbwjoi Street.",
        "edge": "10_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Stxiik BVBA as of 18-09-2007?",
        "answer": "Ogcgwj LLC.",
        "edge": "10_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Ogcgwj LLC in the contract with Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "850 Uqyxwh Square.",
        "edge": "10_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Stxiik BVBA and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "Mattresses.",
        "edge": "10_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Stxiik BVBA and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "51.",
        "edge": "10_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Stxiik BVBA and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "31.",
        "edge": "10_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Stxiik BVBA and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "1581.",
        "edge": "10_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Stxiik BVBA and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "4.",
        "edge": "10_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Stxiik BVBA and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "30.",
        "edge": "10_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Stxiik BVBA and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "25.",
        "edge": "10_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Stxiik BVBA and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "4%.",
        "edge": "10_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Stxiik BVBA and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "000 Ytdnbv Circle.",
        "edge": "10_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Stxiik BVBA and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "10_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Stxiik BVBA and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "10_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Stxiik BVBA and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "2.",
        "edge": "10_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Stxiik BVBA and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "20.",
        "edge": "10_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Stxiik BVBA and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "10.",
        "edge": "10_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Stxiik BVBA and Ogcgwj LLC?",
        "answer": "The State of California.",
        "edge": "10_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Hqopns SRL?",
        "answer": "06-05-2009.",
        "edge": "11_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Hqopns SRL as of 06-05-2009?",
        "answer": "Mlyqwh SRL.",
        "edge": "11_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Mlyqwh SRL in the contract with Hqopns SRL?",
        "answer": "240 Pqpjop Drive.",
        "edge": "11_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Mlyqwh SRL as of 06-05-2009?",
        "answer": "Hqopns SRL.",
        "edge": "11_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Hqopns SRL in the contract with Mlyqwh SRL?",
        "answer": "813 Gilzsr Place.",
        "edge": "11_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Hqopns SRL?",
        "answer": "Bed sheets.",
        "edge": "11_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Hqopns SRL?",
        "answer": "47.",
        "edge": "11_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Hqopns SRL?",
        "answer": "65.",
        "edge": "11_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Hqopns SRL?",
        "answer": "3055.",
        "edge": "11_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Hqopns SRL?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "11_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Hqopns SRL?",
        "answer": "10.",
        "edge": "11_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Hqopns SRL?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "11_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Hqopns SRL?",
        "answer": "3%.",
        "edge": "11_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Hqopns SRL?",
        "answer": "102 Xnbmfp Court.",
        "edge": "11_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Hqopns SRL?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "11_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Hqopns SRL?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "11_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Hqopns SRL?",
        "answer": "2.",
        "edge": "11_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Hqopns SRL?",
        "answer": "10.",
        "edge": "11_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Hqopns SRL?",
        "answer": "12.",
        "edge": "11_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Mlyqwh SRL and Hqopns SRL?",
        "answer": "The State of Florida.",
        "edge": "11_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Gjrtoz AG?",
        "answer": "14-05-2000.",
        "edge": "12_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Gjrtoz AG as of 14-05-2000?",
        "answer": "Gytgwd LLC.",
        "edge": "12_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Gytgwd LLC in the contract with Gjrtoz AG?",
        "answer": "966 Wvdpav Alley.",
        "edge": "12_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Gytgwd LLC as of 14-05-2000?",
        "answer": "Gjrtoz AG.",
        "edge": "12_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Gjrtoz AG in the contract with Gytgwd LLC?",
        "answer": "796 Vtrlha Place.",
        "edge": "12_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Gjrtoz AG?",
        "answer": "Curtains.",
        "edge": "12_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Gjrtoz AG?",
        "answer": "4.",
        "edge": "12_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Gjrtoz AG?",
        "answer": "55.",
        "edge": "12_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Gjrtoz AG?",
        "answer": "220.",
        "edge": "12_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Gjrtoz AG?",
        "answer": "2.",
        "edge": "12_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Gjrtoz AG?",
        "answer": "15.",
        "edge": "12_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Gjrtoz AG?",
        "answer": "15.",
        "edge": "12_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Gjrtoz AG?",
        "answer": "2%.",
        "edge": "12_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Gjrtoz AG?",
        "answer": "548 Lrtfjv Highway.",
        "edge": "12_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Gjrtoz AG?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "12_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Gjrtoz AG?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "12_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Gjrtoz AG?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "12_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Gjrtoz AG?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "12_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Gjrtoz AG?",
        "answer": "14.",
        "edge": "12_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Gytgwd LLC and Gjrtoz AG?",
        "answer": "The State of Georgia.",
        "edge": "12_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Hioruo LLC and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "09-01-2000.",
        "edge": "13_15"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Rlnhbo GmbH as of 09-01-2000?",
        "answer": "Hioruo LLC.",
        "edge": "13_15"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Hioruo LLC in the contract with Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "632 Gwjmfp Street.",
        "edge": "13_15"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Hioruo LLC as of 09-01-2000?",
        "answer": "Rlnhbo GmbH.",
        "edge": "13_15"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Rlnhbo GmbH in the contract with Hioruo LLC?",
        "answer": "903 Dvklfj Boulevard.",
        "edge": "13_15"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Hioruo LLC and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "Refrigerators.",
        "edge": "13_15"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Hioruo LLC and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "35.",
        "edge": "13_15"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Hioruo LLC and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "37.",
        "edge": "13_15"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Hioruo LLC and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "1295.",
        "edge": "13_15"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Hioruo LLC and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "4.",
        "edge": "13_15"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Hioruo LLC and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "10.",
        "edge": "13_15"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Hioruo LLC and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "25.",
        "edge": "13_15"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Hioruo LLC and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "5%.",
        "edge": "13_15"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Hioruo LLC and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "051 Qczuer Lane.",
        "edge": "13_15"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Hioruo LLC and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "13_15"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Hioruo LLC and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "13_15"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Hioruo LLC and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "13_15"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Hioruo LLC and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "10.",
        "edge": "13_15"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Hioruo LLC and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "13_15"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Hioruo LLC and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "The State of North Carolina.",
        "edge": "13_15"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Ntquss BV and Gytgwd LLC?",
        "answer": "21-01-1996.",
        "edge": "14_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Gytgwd LLC as of 21-01-1996?",
        "answer": "Ntquss BV.",
        "edge": "14_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Ntquss BV in the contract with Gytgwd LLC?",
        "answer": "294 Wrhxts Court.",
        "edge": "14_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Ntquss BV as of 21-01-1996?",
        "answer": "Gytgwd LLC.",
        "edge": "14_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Gytgwd LLC in the contract with Ntquss BV?",
        "answer": "966 Wvdpav Alley.",
        "edge": "14_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Ntquss BV and Gytgwd LLC?",
        "answer": "Microwave ovens.",
        "edge": "14_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Ntquss BV and Gytgwd LLC?",
        "answer": "93.",
        "edge": "14_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Ntquss BV and Gytgwd LLC?",
        "answer": "92.",
        "edge": "14_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Ntquss BV and Gytgwd LLC?",
        "answer": "8556.",
        "edge": "14_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Ntquss BV and Gytgwd LLC?",
        "answer": "2.",
        "edge": "14_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Ntquss BV and Gytgwd LLC?",
        "answer": "30.",
        "edge": "14_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Ntquss BV and Gytgwd LLC?",
        "answer": "15.",
        "edge": "14_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Ntquss BV and Gytgwd LLC?",
        "answer": "5%.",
        "edge": "14_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Ntquss BV and Gytgwd LLC?",
        "answer": "467 Hkanoj Square.",
        "edge": "14_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Ntquss BV and Gytgwd LLC?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "14_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Ntquss BV and Gytgwd LLC?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "14_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Ntquss BV and Gytgwd LLC?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "14_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Ntquss BV and Gytgwd LLC?",
        "answer": "20.",
        "edge": "14_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Ntquss BV and Gytgwd LLC?",
        "answer": "9.",
        "edge": "14_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Ntquss BV and Gytgwd LLC?",
        "answer": "The State of California.",
        "edge": "14_16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Hqopns SRL and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "09-10-2014.",
        "edge": "13_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Rlnhbo GmbH as of 09-10-2014?",
        "answer": "Hqopns SRL.",
        "edge": "13_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Hqopns SRL in the contract with Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "813 Gilzsr Place.",
        "edge": "13_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Hqopns SRL as of 09-10-2014?",
        "answer": "Rlnhbo GmbH.",
        "edge": "13_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Rlnhbo GmbH in the contract with Hqopns SRL?",
        "answer": "903 Dvklfj Boulevard.",
        "edge": "13_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Hqopns SRL and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "Kettles.",
        "edge": "13_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Hqopns SRL and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "37.",
        "edge": "13_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Hqopns SRL and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "49.",
        "edge": "13_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Hqopns SRL and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "1813.",
        "edge": "13_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Hqopns SRL and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "3.",
        "edge": "13_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Hqopns SRL and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "15.",
        "edge": "13_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Hqopns SRL and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "25.",
        "edge": "13_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Hqopns SRL and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "5%.",
        "edge": "13_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Hqopns SRL and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "576 Pprhkn Square.",
        "edge": "13_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Hqopns SRL and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "13_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Hqopns SRL and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "13_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Hqopns SRL and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "1.",
        "edge": "13_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Hqopns SRL and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "30.",
        "edge": "13_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Hqopns SRL and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "14.",
        "edge": "13_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Hqopns SRL and Rlnhbo GmbH?",
        "answer": "The State of Florida.",
        "edge": "13_17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "12-07-2014.",
        "edge": "12_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Stxiik BVBA as of 12-07-2014?",
        "answer": "Gjrtoz AG.",
        "edge": "12_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Gjrtoz AG in the contract with Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "796 Vtrlha Place.",
        "edge": "12_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Gjrtoz AG as of 12-07-2014?",
        "answer": "Stxiik BVBA.",
        "edge": "12_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Stxiik BVBA in the contract with Gjrtoz AG?",
        "answer": "818 Xbwjoi Street.",
        "edge": "12_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "Blender.",
        "edge": "12_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "39.",
        "edge": "12_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "74.",
        "edge": "12_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "2886.",
        "edge": "12_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "3.",
        "edge": "12_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "20.",
        "edge": "12_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "30.",
        "edge": "12_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "3%.",
        "edge": "12_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "511 Pkggji Terrace.",
        "edge": "12_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "12_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "12_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "4.",
        "edge": "12_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "20.",
        "edge": "12_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "6.",
        "edge": "12_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Gjrtoz AG and Stxiik BVBA?",
        "answer": "The State of Pennsylvania.",
        "edge": "12_18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Gadwnx SA and Mlyqwh SRL?",
        "answer": "11-06-1987.",
        "edge": "11_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Mlyqwh SRL as of 11-06-1987?",
        "answer": "Gadwnx SA.",
        "edge": "11_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Gadwnx SA in the contract with Mlyqwh SRL?",
        "answer": "290 Gxgyre Alley.",
        "edge": "11_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Gadwnx SA as of 11-06-1987?",
        "answer": "Mlyqwh SRL.",
        "edge": "11_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Mlyqwh SRL in the contract with Gadwnx SA?",
        "answer": "240 Pqpjop Drive.",
        "edge": "11_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Gadwnx SA and Mlyqwh SRL?",
        "answer": "Coffee machines.",
        "edge": "11_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Gadwnx SA and Mlyqwh SRL?",
        "answer": "17.",
        "edge": "11_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Gadwnx SA and Mlyqwh SRL?",
        "answer": "45.",
        "edge": "11_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Gadwnx SA and Mlyqwh SRL?",
        "answer": "765.",
        "edge": "11_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Gadwnx SA and Mlyqwh SRL?",
        "answer": "4.",
        "edge": "11_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Gadwnx SA and Mlyqwh SRL?",
        "answer": "10.",
        "edge": "11_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Gadwnx SA and Mlyqwh SRL?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "11_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Gadwnx SA and Mlyqwh SRL?",
        "answer": "5%.",
        "edge": "11_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Gadwnx SA and Mlyqwh SRL?",
        "answer": "744 Yjimcs Way.",
        "edge": "11_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Gadwnx SA and Mlyqwh SRL?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "11_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Gadwnx SA and Mlyqwh SRL?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "11_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Gadwnx SA and Mlyqwh SRL?",
        "answer": "3.",
        "edge": "11_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Gadwnx SA and Mlyqwh SRL?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "11_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Gadwnx SA and Mlyqwh SRL?",
        "answer": "13.",
        "edge": "11_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Gadwnx SA and Mlyqwh SRL?",
        "answer": "The State of New York.",
        "edge": "11_19"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Qxdylv AG and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "08-02-1981.",
        "edge": "20_21"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Hpqbrj Corp as of 08-02-1981?",
        "answer": "Qxdylv AG.",
        "edge": "20_21"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Qxdylv AG in the contract with Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "067 Hnqhvs Drive.",
        "edge": "20_21"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Qxdylv AG as of 08-02-1981?",
        "answer": "Hpqbrj Corp.",
        "edge": "20_21"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Hpqbrj Corp in the contract with Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "514 Ltxqvq Square.",
        "edge": "20_21"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "Shower gel.",
        "edge": "20_21"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "91.",
        "edge": "20_21"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "24.",
        "edge": "20_21"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "2184.",
        "edge": "20_21"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "20_21"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "10.",
        "edge": "20_21"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "15.",
        "edge": "20_21"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "5%.",
        "edge": "20_21"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "210 Xmgcno Street.",
        "edge": "20_21"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "20_21"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "20_21"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "2.",
        "edge": "20_21"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "10.",
        "edge": "20_21"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "13.",
        "edge": "20_21"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Qxdylv AG and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "The State of Illinois.",
        "edge": "20_21"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "18-09-1986.",
        "edge": "20_22"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Uadpar Ltd as of 18-09-1986?",
        "answer": "Hpqbrj Corp.",
        "edge": "20_22"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Hpqbrj Corp in the contract with Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "514 Ltxqvq Square.",
        "edge": "20_22"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Hpqbrj Corp as of 18-09-1986?",
        "answer": "Uadpar Ltd.",
        "edge": "20_22"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Uadpar Ltd in the contract with Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "928 Tgkpsb Crescent.",
        "edge": "20_22"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "Shampoo.",
        "edge": "20_22"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "63.",
        "edge": "20_22"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "79.",
        "edge": "20_22"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "4977.",
        "edge": "20_22"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "2.",
        "edge": "20_22"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "25.",
        "edge": "20_22"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "30.",
        "edge": "20_22"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "1%.",
        "edge": "20_22"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "600 Irlrdf Lane.",
        "edge": "20_22"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "20_22"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "20_22"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "4.",
        "edge": "20_22"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "25.",
        "edge": "20_22"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "8.",
        "edge": "20_22"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "The State of Texas.",
        "edge": "20_22"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "02-08-1985.",
        "edge": "20_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Hpqbrj Corp as of 02-08-1985?",
        "answer": "Vtybit BVBA.",
        "edge": "20_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Vtybit BVBA in the contract with Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "744 Agrazj Circle.",
        "edge": "20_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Vtybit BVBA as of 02-08-1985?",
        "answer": "Hpqbrj Corp.",
        "edge": "20_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Hpqbrj Corp in the contract with Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "514 Ltxqvq Square.",
        "edge": "20_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "Toothpaste.",
        "edge": "20_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "8.",
        "edge": "20_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "33.",
        "edge": "20_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "264.",
        "edge": "20_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "3.",
        "edge": "20_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "20_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "10.",
        "edge": "20_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "5%.",
        "edge": "20_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "690 Npwwxj Court.",
        "edge": "20_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "20_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "20_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "1.",
        "edge": "20_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "10.",
        "edge": "20_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "7.",
        "edge": "20_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "The State of Illinois.",
        "edge": "20_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "05-10-2008.",
        "edge": "20_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Fqunnm Inc as of 05-10-2008?",
        "answer": "Hpqbrj Corp.",
        "edge": "20_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Hpqbrj Corp in the contract with Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "514 Ltxqvq Square.",
        "edge": "20_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Hpqbrj Corp as of 05-10-2008?",
        "answer": "Fqunnm Inc.",
        "edge": "20_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Fqunnm Inc in the contract with Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "861 Uqkrmg Drive.",
        "edge": "20_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "Toilet paper.",
        "edge": "20_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "2.",
        "edge": "20_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "56.",
        "edge": "20_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "112.",
        "edge": "20_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "3.",
        "edge": "20_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "10.",
        "edge": "20_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "20.",
        "edge": "20_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "4%.",
        "edge": "20_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "399 Pjfoxd Place.",
        "edge": "20_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "20_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "20_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "1.",
        "edge": "20_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "30.",
        "edge": "20_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "9.",
        "edge": "20_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "The State of Georgia.",
        "edge": "20_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "18-01-1995.",
        "edge": "20_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Jwrxqx Ltd as of 18-01-1995?",
        "answer": "Hpqbrj Corp.",
        "edge": "20_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Hpqbrj Corp in the contract with Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "514 Ltxqvq Square.",
        "edge": "20_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Hpqbrj Corp as of 18-01-1995?",
        "answer": "Jwrxqx Ltd.",
        "edge": "20_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Jwrxqx Ltd in the contract with Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "571 Quktvq Square.",
        "edge": "20_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "Hair conditioner.",
        "edge": "20_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "64.",
        "edge": "20_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "63.",
        "edge": "20_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "4032.",
        "edge": "20_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "3.",
        "edge": "20_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "15.",
        "edge": "20_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "20.",
        "edge": "20_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "4%.",
        "edge": "20_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "320 Gyyfng Boulevard.",
        "edge": "20_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "20_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "20_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "4.",
        "edge": "20_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "15.",
        "edge": "20_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "3.",
        "edge": "20_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "The State of Michigan.",
        "edge": "20_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "10-08-2006.",
        "edge": "20_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Hpqbrj Corp as of 10-08-2006?",
        "answer": "Jjbnsm Inc.",
        "edge": "20_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Jjbnsm Inc in the contract with Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "992 Prtqrk Terrace.",
        "edge": "20_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Jjbnsm Inc as of 10-08-2006?",
        "answer": "Hpqbrj Corp.",
        "edge": "20_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Hpqbrj Corp in the contract with Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "514 Ltxqvq Square.",
        "edge": "20_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "Pens.",
        "edge": "20_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "13.",
        "edge": "20_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "55.",
        "edge": "20_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "715.",
        "edge": "20_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "1.",
        "edge": "20_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "25.",
        "edge": "20_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "20_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "1%.",
        "edge": "20_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "022 Tsorhm Highway.",
        "edge": "20_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "20_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "20_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "4.",
        "edge": "20_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "10.",
        "edge": "20_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "10.",
        "edge": "20_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "The State of North Carolina.",
        "edge": "20_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Bathfl Inc and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "13-09-2002.",
        "edge": "20_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Hpqbrj Corp as of 13-09-2002?",
        "answer": "Bathfl Inc.",
        "edge": "20_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Bathfl Inc in the contract with Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "257 Octhfd Way.",
        "edge": "20_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Bathfl Inc as of 13-09-2002?",
        "answer": "Hpqbrj Corp.",
        "edge": "20_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Hpqbrj Corp in the contract with Bathfl Inc?",
        "answer": "514 Ltxqvq Square.",
        "edge": "20_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "Staplers.",
        "edge": "20_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "58.",
        "edge": "20_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "48.",
        "edge": "20_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "2784.",
        "edge": "20_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "20_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "20_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "20.",
        "edge": "20_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "4%.",
        "edge": "20_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "493 Blrfix Lane.",
        "edge": "20_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "20_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "20_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "1.",
        "edge": "20_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "25.",
        "edge": "20_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "9.",
        "edge": "20_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Bathfl Inc and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "The State of North Carolina.",
        "edge": "20_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "21-04-2013.",
        "edge": "20_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Fedafp Corp as of 21-04-2013?",
        "answer": "Hpqbrj Corp.",
        "edge": "20_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Hpqbrj Corp in the contract with Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "514 Ltxqvq Square.",
        "edge": "20_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Hpqbrj Corp as of 21-04-2013?",
        "answer": "Fedafp Corp.",
        "edge": "20_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Fedafp Corp in the contract with Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "289 Qtbgke Square.",
        "edge": "20_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "Scissors.",
        "edge": "20_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "72.",
        "edge": "20_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "89.",
        "edge": "20_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "6408.",
        "edge": "20_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "1.",
        "edge": "20_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "15.",
        "edge": "20_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "20.",
        "edge": "20_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "2%.",
        "edge": "20_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "499 Smlfub Highway.",
        "edge": "20_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "20_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "20_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "2.",
        "edge": "20_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "20.",
        "edge": "20_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "3.",
        "edge": "20_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Hpqbrj Corp and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "The State of California.",
        "edge": "20_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "04-12-2005.",
        "edge": "20_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Hpqbrj Corp as of 04-12-2005?",
        "answer": "Xxkdna PLC.",
        "edge": "20_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Xxkdna PLC in the contract with Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "398 Czcsrf Square.",
        "edge": "20_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Xxkdna PLC as of 04-12-2005?",
        "answer": "Hpqbrj Corp.",
        "edge": "20_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Hpqbrj Corp in the contract with Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "514 Ltxqvq Square.",
        "edge": "20_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "Notebooks.",
        "edge": "20_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "95.",
        "edge": "20_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "3.",
        "edge": "20_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "285.",
        "edge": "20_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "20_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "30.",
        "edge": "20_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "30.",
        "edge": "20_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "1%.",
        "edge": "20_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "979 Pepumh Court.",
        "edge": "20_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "20_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "20_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "20_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "10.",
        "edge": "20_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "3.",
        "edge": "20_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Hpqbrj Corp?",
        "answer": "The State of New York.",
        "edge": "20_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Uadpar Ltd and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "24-09-2004.",
        "edge": "21_22"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Qxdylv AG as of 24-09-2004?",
        "answer": "Uadpar Ltd.",
        "edge": "21_22"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Uadpar Ltd in the contract with Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "928 Tgkpsb Crescent.",
        "edge": "21_22"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Uadpar Ltd as of 24-09-2004?",
        "answer": "Qxdylv AG.",
        "edge": "21_22"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Qxdylv AG in the contract with Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "067 Hnqhvs Drive.",
        "edge": "21_22"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Uadpar Ltd and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "Folders.",
        "edge": "21_22"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Uadpar Ltd and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "1.",
        "edge": "21_22"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Uadpar Ltd and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "77.",
        "edge": "21_22"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Uadpar Ltd and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "77.",
        "edge": "21_22"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Uadpar Ltd and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "3.",
        "edge": "21_22"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Uadpar Ltd and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "25.",
        "edge": "21_22"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Uadpar Ltd and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "30.",
        "edge": "21_22"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Uadpar Ltd and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "2%.",
        "edge": "21_22"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Uadpar Ltd and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "990 Wqszly Road.",
        "edge": "21_22"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Uadpar Ltd and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "21_22"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Uadpar Ltd and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "21_22"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Uadpar Ltd and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "1.",
        "edge": "21_22"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Uadpar Ltd and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "15.",
        "edge": "21_22"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Uadpar Ltd and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "7.",
        "edge": "21_22"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Uadpar Ltd and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "The State of Georgia.",
        "edge": "21_22"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "23-04-1999.",
        "edge": "21_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Qxdylv AG as of 23-04-1999?",
        "answer": "Vtybit BVBA.",
        "edge": "21_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Vtybit BVBA in the contract with Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "744 Agrazj Circle.",
        "edge": "21_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Vtybit BVBA as of 23-04-1999?",
        "answer": "Qxdylv AG.",
        "edge": "21_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Qxdylv AG in the contract with Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "067 Hnqhvs Drive.",
        "edge": "21_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "Soccer balls.",
        "edge": "21_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "50.",
        "edge": "21_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "77.",
        "edge": "21_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "3850.",
        "edge": "21_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "3.",
        "edge": "21_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "15.",
        "edge": "21_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "21_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "1%.",
        "edge": "21_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "774 Kyqydv Avenue.",
        "edge": "21_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "21_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "21_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "2.",
        "edge": "21_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "25.",
        "edge": "21_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "4.",
        "edge": "21_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "The State of Georgia.",
        "edge": "21_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Qxdylv AG and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "13-08-1991.",
        "edge": "21_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Fqunnm Inc as of 13-08-1991?",
        "answer": "Qxdylv AG.",
        "edge": "21_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Qxdylv AG in the contract with Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "067 Hnqhvs Drive.",
        "edge": "21_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Qxdylv AG as of 13-08-1991?",
        "answer": "Fqunnm Inc.",
        "edge": "21_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Fqunnm Inc in the contract with Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "861 Uqkrmg Drive.",
        "edge": "21_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "Tennis rackets.",
        "edge": "21_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "42.",
        "edge": "21_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "75.",
        "edge": "21_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "3150.",
        "edge": "21_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "2.",
        "edge": "21_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "15.",
        "edge": "21_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "25.",
        "edge": "21_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "2%.",
        "edge": "21_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "846 Llugxs Avenue.",
        "edge": "21_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "21_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "21_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "21_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "20.",
        "edge": "21_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "10.",
        "edge": "21_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Qxdylv AG and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "The State of Illinois.",
        "edge": "21_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "30-09-1982.",
        "edge": "21_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Qxdylv AG as of 30-09-1982?",
        "answer": "Jwrxqx Ltd.",
        "edge": "21_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Jwrxqx Ltd in the contract with Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "571 Quktvq Square.",
        "edge": "21_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Jwrxqx Ltd as of 30-09-1982?",
        "answer": "Qxdylv AG.",
        "edge": "21_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Qxdylv AG in the contract with Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "067 Hnqhvs Drive.",
        "edge": "21_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "Golf putters.",
        "edge": "21_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "37.",
        "edge": "21_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "40.",
        "edge": "21_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "1480.",
        "edge": "21_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "2.",
        "edge": "21_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "30.",
        "edge": "21_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "20.",
        "edge": "21_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "2%.",
        "edge": "21_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "259 Jkufzs Drive.",
        "edge": "21_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "21_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "21_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "2.",
        "edge": "21_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "30.",
        "edge": "21_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "8.",
        "edge": "21_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "The State of North Carolina.",
        "edge": "21_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "25-05-1982.",
        "edge": "21_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Qxdylv AG as of 25-05-1982?",
        "answer": "Jjbnsm Inc.",
        "edge": "21_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Jjbnsm Inc in the contract with Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "992 Prtqrk Terrace.",
        "edge": "21_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Jjbnsm Inc as of 25-05-1982?",
        "answer": "Qxdylv AG.",
        "edge": "21_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Qxdylv AG in the contract with Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "067 Hnqhvs Drive.",
        "edge": "21_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "Ski poles.",
        "edge": "21_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "4.",
        "edge": "21_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "88.",
        "edge": "21_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "352.",
        "edge": "21_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "21_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "30.",
        "edge": "21_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "30.",
        "edge": "21_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "5%.",
        "edge": "21_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "459 Bbzkgk Crescent.",
        "edge": "21_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "21_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "21_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "1.",
        "edge": "21_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "30.",
        "edge": "21_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "4.",
        "edge": "21_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "The State of North Carolina.",
        "edge": "21_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Bathfl Inc and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "16-09-2018.",
        "edge": "21_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Qxdylv AG as of 16-09-2018?",
        "answer": "Bathfl Inc.",
        "edge": "21_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Bathfl Inc in the contract with Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "257 Octhfd Way.",
        "edge": "21_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Bathfl Inc as of 16-09-2018?",
        "answer": "Qxdylv AG.",
        "edge": "21_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Qxdylv AG in the contract with Bathfl Inc?",
        "answer": "067 Hnqhvs Drive.",
        "edge": "21_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "Hockey sticks.",
        "edge": "21_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "85.",
        "edge": "21_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "63.",
        "edge": "21_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "5355.",
        "edge": "21_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "21_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "10.",
        "edge": "21_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "20.",
        "edge": "21_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "1%.",
        "edge": "21_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "495 Yitews Avenue.",
        "edge": "21_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "21_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "21_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "3.",
        "edge": "21_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "21_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "11.",
        "edge": "21_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Bathfl Inc and Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "The State of Ohio.",
        "edge": "21_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Qxdylv AG and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "10-10-2008.",
        "edge": "21_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Fedafp Corp as of 10-10-2008?",
        "answer": "Qxdylv AG.",
        "edge": "21_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Qxdylv AG in the contract with Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "067 Hnqhvs Drive.",
        "edge": "21_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Qxdylv AG as of 10-10-2008?",
        "answer": "Fedafp Corp.",
        "edge": "21_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Fedafp Corp in the contract with Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "289 Qtbgke Square.",
        "edge": "21_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "Guitars.",
        "edge": "21_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "61.",
        "edge": "21_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "64.",
        "edge": "21_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "3904.",
        "edge": "21_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "4.",
        "edge": "21_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "30.",
        "edge": "21_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "15.",
        "edge": "21_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "3%.",
        "edge": "21_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "214 Anwbwq Lane.",
        "edge": "21_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "21_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "21_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "21_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "21_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "14.",
        "edge": "21_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Qxdylv AG and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "The State of Texas.",
        "edge": "21_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Qxdylv AG and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "20-10-1990.",
        "edge": "21_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Xxkdna PLC as of 20-10-1990?",
        "answer": "Qxdylv AG.",
        "edge": "21_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Qxdylv AG in the contract with Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "067 Hnqhvs Drive.",
        "edge": "21_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Qxdylv AG as of 20-10-1990?",
        "answer": "Xxkdna PLC.",
        "edge": "21_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Xxkdna PLC in the contract with Qxdylv AG?",
        "answer": "398 Czcsrf Square.",
        "edge": "21_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "Piano.",
        "edge": "21_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "65.",
        "edge": "21_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "30.",
        "edge": "21_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "1950.",
        "edge": "21_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "1.",
        "edge": "21_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "10.",
        "edge": "21_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "15.",
        "edge": "21_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "4%.",
        "edge": "21_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "076 Octpde Court.",
        "edge": "21_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "21_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "21_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "3.",
        "edge": "21_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "15.",
        "edge": "21_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Qxdylv AG and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "3.",
        "edge": "21_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Qxdylv AG and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "The State of Georgia.",
        "edge": "21_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "25-07-1995.",
        "edge": "22_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Uadpar Ltd as of 25-07-1995?",
        "answer": "Vtybit BVBA.",
        "edge": "22_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Vtybit BVBA in the contract with Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "744 Agrazj Circle.",
        "edge": "22_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Vtybit BVBA as of 25-07-1995?",
        "answer": "Uadpar Ltd.",
        "edge": "22_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Uadpar Ltd in the contract with Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "928 Tgkpsb Crescent.",
        "edge": "22_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "Violins.",
        "edge": "22_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "44.",
        "edge": "22_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "57.",
        "edge": "22_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "2508.",
        "edge": "22_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "22_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "30.",
        "edge": "22_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "30.",
        "edge": "22_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "3%.",
        "edge": "22_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "749 Trybov Street.",
        "edge": "22_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "22_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "22_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "1.",
        "edge": "22_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "25.",
        "edge": "22_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "8.",
        "edge": "22_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "The State of Georgia.",
        "edge": "22_23"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "07-10-1989.",
        "edge": "22_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Uadpar Ltd as of 07-10-1989?",
        "answer": "Fqunnm Inc.",
        "edge": "22_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Fqunnm Inc in the contract with Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "861 Uqkrmg Drive.",
        "edge": "22_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Fqunnm Inc as of 07-10-1989?",
        "answer": "Uadpar Ltd.",
        "edge": "22_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Uadpar Ltd in the contract with Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "928 Tgkpsb Crescent.",
        "edge": "22_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "Drums.",
        "edge": "22_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "75.",
        "edge": "22_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "75.",
        "edge": "22_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "5625.",
        "edge": "22_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "22_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "15.",
        "edge": "22_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "20.",
        "edge": "22_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "5%.",
        "edge": "22_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "693 Znfxku Way.",
        "edge": "22_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "22_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "22_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "2.",
        "edge": "22_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "30.",
        "edge": "22_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "10.",
        "edge": "22_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "The State of Texas.",
        "edge": "22_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "28-09-2008.",
        "edge": "22_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Uadpar Ltd as of 28-09-2008?",
        "answer": "Jwrxqx Ltd.",
        "edge": "22_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Jwrxqx Ltd in the contract with Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "571 Quktvq Square.",
        "edge": "22_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Jwrxqx Ltd as of 28-09-2008?",
        "answer": "Uadpar Ltd.",
        "edge": "22_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Uadpar Ltd in the contract with Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "928 Tgkpsb Crescent.",
        "edge": "22_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "Flutes.",
        "edge": "22_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "87.",
        "edge": "22_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "71.",
        "edge": "22_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "6177.",
        "edge": "22_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "1.",
        "edge": "22_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "22_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "10.",
        "edge": "22_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "3%.",
        "edge": "22_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "015 Hfmwqp Drive.",
        "edge": "22_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "22_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "22_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "22_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "30.",
        "edge": "22_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "3.",
        "edge": "22_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "The State of New York.",
        "edge": "22_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Uadpar Ltd and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "09-08-1994.",
        "edge": "22_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Jjbnsm Inc as of 09-08-1994?",
        "answer": "Uadpar Ltd.",
        "edge": "22_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Uadpar Ltd in the contract with Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "928 Tgkpsb Crescent.",
        "edge": "22_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Uadpar Ltd as of 09-08-1994?",
        "answer": "Jjbnsm Inc.",
        "edge": "22_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Jjbnsm Inc in the contract with Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "992 Prtqrk Terrace.",
        "edge": "22_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Uadpar Ltd and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "Paintings.",
        "edge": "22_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Uadpar Ltd and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "53.",
        "edge": "22_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Uadpar Ltd and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "25.",
        "edge": "22_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Uadpar Ltd and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "1325.",
        "edge": "22_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Uadpar Ltd and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "3.",
        "edge": "22_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Uadpar Ltd and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "25.",
        "edge": "22_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Uadpar Ltd and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "10.",
        "edge": "22_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Uadpar Ltd and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "1%.",
        "edge": "22_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Uadpar Ltd and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "138 Usbnhv Lane.",
        "edge": "22_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Uadpar Ltd and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "22_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Uadpar Ltd and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "22_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Uadpar Ltd and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "4.",
        "edge": "22_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Uadpar Ltd and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "30.",
        "edge": "22_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Uadpar Ltd and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "3.",
        "edge": "22_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Uadpar Ltd and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "The State of Ohio.",
        "edge": "22_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Bathfl Inc and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "28-11-1988.",
        "edge": "22_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Uadpar Ltd as of 28-11-1988?",
        "answer": "Bathfl Inc.",
        "edge": "22_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Bathfl Inc in the contract with Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "257 Octhfd Way.",
        "edge": "22_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Bathfl Inc as of 28-11-1988?",
        "answer": "Uadpar Ltd.",
        "edge": "22_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Uadpar Ltd in the contract with Bathfl Inc?",
        "answer": "928 Tgkpsb Crescent.",
        "edge": "22_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "Sculptures.",
        "edge": "22_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "84.",
        "edge": "22_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "59.",
        "edge": "22_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "4956.",
        "edge": "22_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "22_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "15.",
        "edge": "22_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "15.",
        "edge": "22_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "2%.",
        "edge": "22_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "470 Wmiyqf Drive.",
        "edge": "22_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "22_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "22_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "22_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "20.",
        "edge": "22_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "12.",
        "edge": "22_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Bathfl Inc and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "The State of Illinois.",
        "edge": "22_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Fedafp Corp and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "31-08-2002.",
        "edge": "22_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Uadpar Ltd as of 31-08-2002?",
        "answer": "Fedafp Corp.",
        "edge": "22_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Fedafp Corp in the contract with Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "289 Qtbgke Square.",
        "edge": "22_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Fedafp Corp as of 31-08-2002?",
        "answer": "Uadpar Ltd.",
        "edge": "22_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Uadpar Ltd in the contract with Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "928 Tgkpsb Crescent.",
        "edge": "22_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "Photographs.",
        "edge": "22_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "40.",
        "edge": "22_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "4.",
        "edge": "22_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "160.",
        "edge": "22_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "1.",
        "edge": "22_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "22_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "30.",
        "edge": "22_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "4%.",
        "edge": "22_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "212 Fypxjd Street.",
        "edge": "22_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "22_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "22_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "4.",
        "edge": "22_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "22_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "14.",
        "edge": "22_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Fedafp Corp and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "The State of Pennsylvania.",
        "edge": "22_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "23-11-2017.",
        "edge": "22_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Uadpar Ltd as of 23-11-2017?",
        "answer": "Xxkdna PLC.",
        "edge": "22_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Xxkdna PLC in the contract with Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "398 Czcsrf Square.",
        "edge": "22_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Xxkdna PLC as of 23-11-2017?",
        "answer": "Uadpar Ltd.",
        "edge": "22_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Uadpar Ltd in the contract with Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "928 Tgkpsb Crescent.",
        "edge": "22_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "Drawings.",
        "edge": "22_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "49.",
        "edge": "22_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "7.",
        "edge": "22_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "343.",
        "edge": "22_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "2.",
        "edge": "22_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "22_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "20.",
        "edge": "22_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "2%.",
        "edge": "22_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "155 Kuiuus Terrace.",
        "edge": "22_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "22_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "22_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "2.",
        "edge": "22_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "25.",
        "edge": "22_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "6.",
        "edge": "22_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Uadpar Ltd?",
        "answer": "The State of Florida.",
        "edge": "22_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "05-12-2001.",
        "edge": "23_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Vtybit BVBA as of 05-12-2001?",
        "answer": "Fqunnm Inc.",
        "edge": "23_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Fqunnm Inc in the contract with Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "861 Uqkrmg Drive.",
        "edge": "23_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Fqunnm Inc as of 05-12-2001?",
        "answer": "Vtybit BVBA.",
        "edge": "23_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Vtybit BVBA in the contract with Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "744 Agrazj Circle.",
        "edge": "23_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "Prints.",
        "edge": "23_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "35.",
        "edge": "23_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "71.",
        "edge": "23_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "2485.",
        "edge": "23_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "1.",
        "edge": "23_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "10.",
        "edge": "23_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "23_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "2%.",
        "edge": "23_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "031 Xzdtma Boulevard.",
        "edge": "23_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "23_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "23_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "2.",
        "edge": "23_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "15.",
        "edge": "23_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "4.",
        "edge": "23_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "The State of Michigan.",
        "edge": "23_24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "11-04-2002.",
        "edge": "23_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Vtybit BVBA as of 11-04-2002?",
        "answer": "Jwrxqx Ltd.",
        "edge": "23_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Jwrxqx Ltd in the contract with Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "571 Quktvq Square.",
        "edge": "23_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Jwrxqx Ltd as of 11-04-2002?",
        "answer": "Vtybit BVBA.",
        "edge": "23_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Vtybit BVBA in the contract with Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "744 Agrazj Circle.",
        "edge": "23_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "Patio tiles.",
        "edge": "23_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "96.",
        "edge": "23_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "62.",
        "edge": "23_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "5952.",
        "edge": "23_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "3.",
        "edge": "23_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "23_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "20.",
        "edge": "23_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "4%.",
        "edge": "23_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "921 Idewpc Way.",
        "edge": "23_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "23_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "23_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "3.",
        "edge": "23_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "25.",
        "edge": "23_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "23_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "The State of California.",
        "edge": "23_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "07-06-2014.",
        "edge": "23_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Jjbnsm Inc as of 07-06-2014?",
        "answer": "Vtybit BVBA.",
        "edge": "23_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Vtybit BVBA in the contract with Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "744 Agrazj Circle.",
        "edge": "23_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Vtybit BVBA as of 07-06-2014?",
        "answer": "Jjbnsm Inc.",
        "edge": "23_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Jjbnsm Inc in the contract with Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "992 Prtqrk Terrace.",
        "edge": "23_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "Gardening tools.",
        "edge": "23_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "32.",
        "edge": "23_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "81.",
        "edge": "23_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "2592.",
        "edge": "23_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "23_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "20.",
        "edge": "23_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "15.",
        "edge": "23_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "4%.",
        "edge": "23_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "254 Kmoijc Crescent.",
        "edge": "23_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "23_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "23_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "1.",
        "edge": "23_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "23_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "6.",
        "edge": "23_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "The State of North Carolina.",
        "edge": "23_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Bathfl Inc and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "10-04-2014.",
        "edge": "23_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Vtybit BVBA as of 10-04-2014?",
        "answer": "Bathfl Inc.",
        "edge": "23_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Bathfl Inc in the contract with Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "257 Octhfd Way.",
        "edge": "23_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Bathfl Inc as of 10-04-2014?",
        "answer": "Vtybit BVBA.",
        "edge": "23_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Vtybit BVBA in the contract with Bathfl Inc?",
        "answer": "744 Agrazj Circle.",
        "edge": "23_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "Grass seeds.",
        "edge": "23_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "90.",
        "edge": "23_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "37.",
        "edge": "23_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "3330.",
        "edge": "23_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "3.",
        "edge": "23_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "25.",
        "edge": "23_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "10.",
        "edge": "23_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "4%.",
        "edge": "23_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "646 Fwgqye Street.",
        "edge": "23_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "23_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "23_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "3.",
        "edge": "23_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "25.",
        "edge": "23_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "11.",
        "edge": "23_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Bathfl Inc and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "The State of Michigan.",
        "edge": "23_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Fedafp Corp and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "28-10-1999.",
        "edge": "23_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Vtybit BVBA as of 28-10-1999?",
        "answer": "Fedafp Corp.",
        "edge": "23_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Fedafp Corp in the contract with Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "289 Qtbgke Square.",
        "edge": "23_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Fedafp Corp as of 28-10-1999?",
        "answer": "Vtybit BVBA.",
        "edge": "23_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Vtybit BVBA in the contract with Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "744 Agrazj Circle.",
        "edge": "23_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "Fertilizers.",
        "edge": "23_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "82.",
        "edge": "23_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "32.",
        "edge": "23_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "2624.",
        "edge": "23_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "2.",
        "edge": "23_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "15.",
        "edge": "23_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "15.",
        "edge": "23_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "1%.",
        "edge": "23_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "700 Yegoiy Street.",
        "edge": "23_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "23_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "23_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "1.",
        "edge": "23_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "30.",
        "edge": "23_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "11.",
        "edge": "23_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Fedafp Corp and Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "The State of Ohio.",
        "edge": "23_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "03-12-2018.",
        "edge": "23_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Xxkdna PLC as of 03-12-2018?",
        "answer": "Vtybit BVBA.",
        "edge": "23_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Vtybit BVBA in the contract with Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "744 Agrazj Circle.",
        "edge": "23_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Vtybit BVBA as of 03-12-2018?",
        "answer": "Xxkdna PLC.",
        "edge": "23_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Xxkdna PLC in the contract with Vtybit BVBA?",
        "answer": "398 Czcsrf Square.",
        "edge": "23_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "Plant pots.",
        "edge": "23_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "39.",
        "edge": "23_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "56.",
        "edge": "23_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "2184.",
        "edge": "23_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "2.",
        "edge": "23_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "25.",
        "edge": "23_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "10.",
        "edge": "23_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "2%.",
        "edge": "23_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "514 Sluviz Boulevard.",
        "edge": "23_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "23_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "23_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "1.",
        "edge": "23_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "25.",
        "edge": "23_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "13.",
        "edge": "23_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Vtybit BVBA and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "The State of North Carolina.",
        "edge": "23_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "29-07-1996.",
        "edge": "24_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Fqunnm Inc as of 29-07-1996?",
        "answer": "Jwrxqx Ltd.",
        "edge": "24_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Jwrxqx Ltd in the contract with Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "571 Quktvq Square.",
        "edge": "24_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Jwrxqx Ltd as of 29-07-1996?",
        "answer": "Fqunnm Inc.",
        "edge": "24_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Fqunnm Inc in the contract with Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "861 Uqkrmg Drive.",
        "edge": "24_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "Sandwich.",
        "edge": "24_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "58.",
        "edge": "24_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "6.",
        "edge": "24_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "348.",
        "edge": "24_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "4.",
        "edge": "24_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "20.",
        "edge": "24_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "15.",
        "edge": "24_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "4%.",
        "edge": "24_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "987 Naxhqc Terrace.",
        "edge": "24_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "24_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "24_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "4.",
        "edge": "24_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "30.",
        "edge": "24_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "7.",
        "edge": "24_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "The State of Michigan.",
        "edge": "24_25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "29-07-2012.",
        "edge": "24_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Fqunnm Inc as of 29-07-2012?",
        "answer": "Jjbnsm Inc.",
        "edge": "24_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Jjbnsm Inc in the contract with Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "992 Prtqrk Terrace.",
        "edge": "24_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Jjbnsm Inc as of 29-07-2012?",
        "answer": "Fqunnm Inc.",
        "edge": "24_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Fqunnm Inc in the contract with Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "861 Uqkrmg Drive.",
        "edge": "24_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "Pizza.",
        "edge": "24_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "45.",
        "edge": "24_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "82.",
        "edge": "24_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "3690.",
        "edge": "24_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "24_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "10.",
        "edge": "24_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "20.",
        "edge": "24_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "4%.",
        "edge": "24_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "495 Rjbirj Crescent.",
        "edge": "24_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "24_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "24_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "4.",
        "edge": "24_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "25.",
        "edge": "24_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "12.",
        "edge": "24_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "The State of Illinois.",
        "edge": "24_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Bathfl Inc?",
        "answer": "09-05-1993.",
        "edge": "24_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Bathfl Inc as of 09-05-1993?",
        "answer": "Fqunnm Inc.",
        "edge": "24_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Fqunnm Inc in the contract with Bathfl Inc?",
        "answer": "861 Uqkrmg Drive.",
        "edge": "24_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Fqunnm Inc as of 09-05-1993?",
        "answer": "Bathfl Inc.",
        "edge": "24_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Bathfl Inc in the contract with Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "257 Octhfd Way.",
        "edge": "24_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Bathfl Inc?",
        "answer": "Steaks.",
        "edge": "24_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Bathfl Inc?",
        "answer": "96.",
        "edge": "24_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Bathfl Inc?",
        "answer": "44.",
        "edge": "24_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Bathfl Inc?",
        "answer": "4224.",
        "edge": "24_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Bathfl Inc?",
        "answer": "4.",
        "edge": "24_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Bathfl Inc?",
        "answer": "20.",
        "edge": "24_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Bathfl Inc?",
        "answer": "10.",
        "edge": "24_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Bathfl Inc?",
        "answer": "4%.",
        "edge": "24_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Bathfl Inc?",
        "answer": "325 Ruxati Court.",
        "edge": "24_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Bathfl Inc?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "24_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Bathfl Inc?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "24_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Bathfl Inc?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "24_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Bathfl Inc?",
        "answer": "25.",
        "edge": "24_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Bathfl Inc?",
        "answer": "4.",
        "edge": "24_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Fqunnm Inc and Bathfl Inc?",
        "answer": "The State of Illinois.",
        "edge": "24_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Fedafp Corp and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "19-01-2003.",
        "edge": "24_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Fqunnm Inc as of 19-01-2003?",
        "answer": "Fedafp Corp.",
        "edge": "24_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Fedafp Corp in the contract with Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "289 Qtbgke Square.",
        "edge": "24_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Fedafp Corp as of 19-01-2003?",
        "answer": "Fqunnm Inc.",
        "edge": "24_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Fqunnm Inc in the contract with Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "861 Uqkrmg Drive.",
        "edge": "24_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "Sushi.",
        "edge": "24_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "39.",
        "edge": "24_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "82.",
        "edge": "24_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "3198.",
        "edge": "24_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "3.",
        "edge": "24_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "15.",
        "edge": "24_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "10.",
        "edge": "24_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "1%.",
        "edge": "24_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "908 Fclrma Highway.",
        "edge": "24_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "24_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "24_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "1.",
        "edge": "24_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "25.",
        "edge": "24_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "7.",
        "edge": "24_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Fedafp Corp and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "The State of New York.",
        "edge": "24_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "26-12-1989.",
        "edge": "24_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Fqunnm Inc as of 26-12-1989?",
        "answer": "Xxkdna PLC.",
        "edge": "24_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Xxkdna PLC in the contract with Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "398 Czcsrf Square.",
        "edge": "24_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Xxkdna PLC as of 26-12-1989?",
        "answer": "Fqunnm Inc.",
        "edge": "24_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Fqunnm Inc in the contract with Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "861 Uqkrmg Drive.",
        "edge": "24_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "Burgers.",
        "edge": "24_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "48.",
        "edge": "24_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "28.",
        "edge": "24_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "1344.",
        "edge": "24_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "2.",
        "edge": "24_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "20.",
        "edge": "24_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "25.",
        "edge": "24_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "5%.",
        "edge": "24_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "485 Zgaidg Place.",
        "edge": "24_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "24_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "24_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "24_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "24_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "4.",
        "edge": "24_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Xxkdna PLC and Fqunnm Inc?",
        "answer": "The State of Texas.",
        "edge": "24_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "20-07-1995.",
        "edge": "25_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Jwrxqx Ltd as of 20-07-1995?",
        "answer": "Jjbnsm Inc.",
        "edge": "25_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Jjbnsm Inc in the contract with Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "992 Prtqrk Terrace.",
        "edge": "25_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Jjbnsm Inc as of 20-07-1995?",
        "answer": "Jwrxqx Ltd.",
        "edge": "25_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Jwrxqx Ltd in the contract with Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "571 Quktvq Square.",
        "edge": "25_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "Bikes.",
        "edge": "25_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "84.",
        "edge": "25_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "54.",
        "edge": "25_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "4536.",
        "edge": "25_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "4.",
        "edge": "25_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "30.",
        "edge": "25_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "25_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "1%.",
        "edge": "25_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "255 Jtcnbh Way.",
        "edge": "25_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "25_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "25_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "4.",
        "edge": "25_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "25.",
        "edge": "25_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "12.",
        "edge": "25_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "The State of Ohio.",
        "edge": "25_26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Bathfl Inc and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "07-09-2001.",
        "edge": "25_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Jwrxqx Ltd as of 07-09-2001?",
        "answer": "Bathfl Inc.",
        "edge": "25_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Bathfl Inc in the contract with Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "257 Octhfd Way.",
        "edge": "25_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Bathfl Inc as of 07-09-2001?",
        "answer": "Jwrxqx Ltd.",
        "edge": "25_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Jwrxqx Ltd in the contract with Bathfl Inc?",
        "answer": "571 Quktvq Square.",
        "edge": "25_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "Skateboards.",
        "edge": "25_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "7.",
        "edge": "25_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "65.",
        "edge": "25_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "455.",
        "edge": "25_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "1.",
        "edge": "25_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "30.",
        "edge": "25_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "25.",
        "edge": "25_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "4%.",
        "edge": "25_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "127 Kkkwjf Street.",
        "edge": "25_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "25_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "25_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "4.",
        "edge": "25_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "20.",
        "edge": "25_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "12.",
        "edge": "25_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Bathfl Inc and Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "The State of New York.",
        "edge": "25_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "07-06-2017.",
        "edge": "25_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Fedafp Corp as of 07-06-2017?",
        "answer": "Jwrxqx Ltd.",
        "edge": "25_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Jwrxqx Ltd in the contract with Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "571 Quktvq Square.",
        "edge": "25_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Jwrxqx Ltd as of 07-06-2017?",
        "answer": "Fedafp Corp.",
        "edge": "25_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Fedafp Corp in the contract with Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "289 Qtbgke Square.",
        "edge": "25_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "Scooters.",
        "edge": "25_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "75.",
        "edge": "25_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "84.",
        "edge": "25_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "6300.",
        "edge": "25_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "4.",
        "edge": "25_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "20.",
        "edge": "25_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "20.",
        "edge": "25_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "2%.",
        "edge": "25_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "641 Rzziqf Square.",
        "edge": "25_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "25_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "25_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "3.",
        "edge": "25_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "15.",
        "edge": "25_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "14.",
        "edge": "25_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "The State of California.",
        "edge": "25_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "15-01-2014.",
        "edge": "25_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Xxkdna PLC as of 15-01-2014?",
        "answer": "Jwrxqx Ltd.",
        "edge": "25_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Jwrxqx Ltd in the contract with Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "571 Quktvq Square.",
        "edge": "25_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Jwrxqx Ltd as of 15-01-2014?",
        "answer": "Xxkdna PLC.",
        "edge": "25_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Xxkdna PLC in the contract with Jwrxqx Ltd?",
        "answer": "398 Czcsrf Square.",
        "edge": "25_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "Rollerblades.",
        "edge": "25_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "97.",
        "edge": "25_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "66.",
        "edge": "25_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "6402.",
        "edge": "25_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "3.",
        "edge": "25_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "15.",
        "edge": "25_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "10.",
        "edge": "25_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "5%.",
        "edge": "25_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "711 Asqdmd Court.",
        "edge": "25_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "25_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "25_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "3.",
        "edge": "25_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "25_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "7.",
        "edge": "25_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Jwrxqx Ltd and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "The State of Florida.",
        "edge": "25_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Bathfl Inc and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "26-07-2019.",
        "edge": "26_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Jjbnsm Inc as of 26-07-2019?",
        "answer": "Bathfl Inc.",
        "edge": "26_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Bathfl Inc in the contract with Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "257 Octhfd Way.",
        "edge": "26_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Bathfl Inc as of 26-07-2019?",
        "answer": "Jjbnsm Inc.",
        "edge": "26_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Jjbnsm Inc in the contract with Bathfl Inc?",
        "answer": "992 Prtqrk Terrace.",
        "edge": "26_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "Cars.",
        "edge": "26_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "12.",
        "edge": "26_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "3.",
        "edge": "26_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "36.",
        "edge": "26_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "26_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "15.",
        "edge": "26_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "30.",
        "edge": "26_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "5%.",
        "edge": "26_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "361 Dvtkug Way.",
        "edge": "26_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "26_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "26_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "3.",
        "edge": "26_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "15.",
        "edge": "26_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "7.",
        "edge": "26_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Bathfl Inc and Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "The State of Pennsylvania.",
        "edge": "26_27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "16-01-2002.",
        "edge": "26_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Fedafp Corp as of 16-01-2002?",
        "answer": "Jjbnsm Inc.",
        "edge": "26_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Jjbnsm Inc in the contract with Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "992 Prtqrk Terrace.",
        "edge": "26_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Jjbnsm Inc as of 16-01-2002?",
        "answer": "Fedafp Corp.",
        "edge": "26_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Fedafp Corp in the contract with Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "289 Qtbgke Square.",
        "edge": "26_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "Dog beds.",
        "edge": "26_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "6.",
        "edge": "26_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "17.",
        "edge": "26_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "102.",
        "edge": "26_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "26_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "30.",
        "edge": "26_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "30.",
        "edge": "26_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "1%.",
        "edge": "26_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "862 Xnjpqt Drive.",
        "edge": "26_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "26_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "26_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "3.",
        "edge": "26_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "26_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "12.",
        "edge": "26_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "The State of California.",
        "edge": "26_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "19-09-2011.",
        "edge": "26_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Xxkdna PLC as of 19-09-2011?",
        "answer": "Jjbnsm Inc.",
        "edge": "26_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Jjbnsm Inc in the contract with Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "992 Prtqrk Terrace.",
        "edge": "26_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Jjbnsm Inc as of 19-09-2011?",
        "answer": "Xxkdna PLC.",
        "edge": "26_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Xxkdna PLC in the contract with Jjbnsm Inc?",
        "answer": "398 Czcsrf Square.",
        "edge": "26_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "Cat trees.",
        "edge": "26_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "36.",
        "edge": "26_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "61.",
        "edge": "26_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "2196.",
        "edge": "26_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "26_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "25.",
        "edge": "26_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "20.",
        "edge": "26_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "4%.",
        "edge": "26_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "934 Cgfqza Court.",
        "edge": "26_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "26_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "26_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "2.",
        "edge": "26_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "15.",
        "edge": "26_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "14.",
        "edge": "26_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Jjbnsm Inc and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "The State of Ohio.",
        "edge": "26_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Bathfl Inc and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "24-10-1995.",
        "edge": "27_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Fedafp Corp as of 24-10-1995?",
        "answer": "Bathfl Inc.",
        "edge": "27_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Bathfl Inc in the contract with Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "257 Octhfd Way.",
        "edge": "27_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Bathfl Inc as of 24-10-1995?",
        "answer": "Fedafp Corp.",
        "edge": "27_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Fedafp Corp in the contract with Bathfl Inc?",
        "answer": "289 Qtbgke Square.",
        "edge": "27_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "Fish tanks.",
        "edge": "27_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "4.",
        "edge": "27_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "31.",
        "edge": "27_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "124.",
        "edge": "27_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "1.",
        "edge": "27_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "10.",
        "edge": "27_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "10.",
        "edge": "27_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "3%.",
        "edge": "27_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "437 Ldsrmb Square.",
        "edge": "27_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "27_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "27_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "2.",
        "edge": "27_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "10.",
        "edge": "27_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "13.",
        "edge": "27_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Bathfl Inc and Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "The State of California.",
        "edge": "27_28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Bathfl Inc and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "11-06-2016.",
        "edge": "27_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Xxkdna PLC as of 11-06-2016?",
        "answer": "Bathfl Inc.",
        "edge": "27_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Bathfl Inc in the contract with Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "257 Octhfd Way.",
        "edge": "27_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Bathfl Inc as of 11-06-2016?",
        "answer": "Xxkdna PLC.",
        "edge": "27_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Xxkdna PLC in the contract with Bathfl Inc?",
        "answer": "398 Czcsrf Square.",
        "edge": "27_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "Bird cages.",
        "edge": "27_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "27.",
        "edge": "27_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "82.",
        "edge": "27_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "2214.",
        "edge": "27_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "27_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "20.",
        "edge": "27_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "20.",
        "edge": "27_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "2%.",
        "edge": "27_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "940 Dzrapf Road.",
        "edge": "27_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "Seller.",
        "edge": "27_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "27_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "3.",
        "edge": "27_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "25.",
        "edge": "27_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Bathfl Inc and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "11.",
        "edge": "27_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Bathfl Inc and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "The State of California.",
        "edge": "27_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the effective date of the contract between Fedafp Corp and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "16-02-1993.",
        "edge": "28_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the seller in the contract with Xxkdna PLC as of 16-02-1993?",
        "answer": "Fedafp Corp.",
        "edge": "28_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Fedafp Corp in the contract with Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "289 Qtbgke Square.",
        "edge": "28_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the customer in the contract with Fedafp Corp as of 16-02-1993?",
        "answer": "Xxkdna PLC.",
        "edge": "28_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of Xxkdna PLC in the contract with Fedafp Corp?",
        "answer": "398 Czcsrf Square.",
        "edge": "28_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the good that the seller was selling to the customer based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "Hamster wheels.",
        "edge": "28_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the quantity of the good being sold based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "24.",
        "edge": "28_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unit price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "73.",
        "edge": "28_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total price in dollars of the good being sold based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "1752.",
        "edge": "28_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "By how many days after the delivery time must the seller provide the customer with an invoice based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "2.",
        "edge": "28_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days must the invoice be paid in full based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "20.",
        "edge": "28_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "After how many days would unpaid balances incur a late payment penalty based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "5.",
        "edge": "28_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the late payment interest rate based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "4%.",
        "edge": "28_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the address of delivery based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "304 Mdgayy Alley.",
        "edge": "28_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would decide the shipping method based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "28_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who would be responsible for the costs of the shipment based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "Customer.",
        "edge": "28_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the general warranty period in years based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "2.",
        "edge": "28_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "Within how many days of discovering a defect must the customer notify the seller in writing in the event of a breach of warranty based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "10.",
        "edge": "28_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the duration of the cooling-off period in days based on the contract between Fedafp Corp and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "3.",
        "edge": "28_29"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jurisdiction's laws govern the contract between Fedafp Corp and Xxkdna PLC?",
        "answer": "The State of Illinois.",
        "edge": "28_29"
    }
]